Okay, folks...can human igneous you can.
Well, hello, it's couple minutes of to...can starks.
Hello, everybody welcome.
My name is your
...creating...on the argentine specifically working on other
...services.
And, today I'm going to would you do about...running web
...applications...as rob service we announce...service couple weeks ago
is was recapping the keynote as well and some cool demos are related to
...services...was great I guess as I said my name is your hungry
...this my email work and the twitter if...to follow.
I'm supposed to remind you that you need to submit evaluation for each regulations
students this...anyway this is good for us give us feedback we can learn for
the next time we presenting on-base to basal anything can do to helpers will be good.
So, model of topics imaginable
of content of we'll talk a little bit about up services we've seen in the keynote
...morewe'll take a look at some travel...them...kind of for canonical demo
that we like to show and we'll talk...service environment which is...preview which is a new feature that
we actually announcing today probably in this session for the first-time although
it's I believe the blogs and the portals already updated if you've seen
that are will have time for qa dn but if you have any questions feel free to just
...whatever he wants to raise your
...the lights...have to showed as well.
All right so let's start so up service
rate one integrated offering combining basically web app mobile up logic
...api...now you can have all of themtogether.
Basically up services recording gives you almost everything you need to do to
run a...app in your...for application for your company your
...replies or...whatever you guys are...sauces well we're working with some vendors...working with some
partners working with a lot of customers grading...running on up services.
And, basically that's what I think you guys have seen this
slide or a similar slide doing the keynote from the of mistaking
...kind of...that view and the reason we like to show that
view because for us we can basically talk about when you come to compose
...you can use web api is kind of the glue to
peace all the all the pieces together to bring all the pieces together so...web apps
...logic obscure mobile apps all of them can just use a api
apps and be happy with it so we've seen it in the keynote.
Some of that the demos with the...three-d printing and all that which one
very world however when you come to actually sorry?
...however cool anyway specifically for...reason I'm showing this
...right here is that there are a lot of other slighted will talk to-you about how you actually going to run
...actually going to build applications like code and all of that code examples
and anything like that right...by the way...just don't leave but right now it...have
...talking about...architecture of the observes but basically there's a bunch
of sessions about development mobile logic up api...you and
...through how to build the app what I want to focuses mostly how you once you have an
app what you do...how do you run it's what you make sure that runs well it runs
at scale it's highly available what make sure what you need to do to make
it be able to run across multiple regions as well what do you do two-run the...that all the
...developers in the...building...lot
...authors overlooking that and we just go ahead and just drill down and building cool stuff
which is important but I hope this session will have benefits...we look at platform
view when we look at we think of how do we run this thing so we took actually the web apps and put
...the bottom because.
Everything now is kind of a web up so mobile and api are
essentially web applications what used to be called websites and
they are kind of special because we just give
them some special treatment we give them some extra stuff on top but literally
...the runtime...hosted where the running...their running the running on the same...that
...whereabouts a and logic up's has a special...doing all that.
So, before going to the demo quick show of hands
...already using a...websites or web apps...the web
...good majority who's doing it and production
for real like all right also majorities for vacancy okay three so
...try api apps...stuff like that you...
...many work for enough so now I'm going to have a lot of different in terms of experience when you come to
...as I said they're all eventually websites you can actually go ahead and see
that underline work-site.
Okay,
so, I want to go through a demo which will be different than what we've seen in the.
In the keynote and.
Cool so although started demo do everything in private browsing makes
everybody's life easier when it comes to login all that and you'll see it in a second.
I would like to go ahead and talk about the travel up so this is a travel...that we have created
and the first thing you see to in order to get into trouble up you need to be able to login...important will cover
ducts...just go in going to put my credentials.
So, they do that you'll...a get redirected.
...for zooming little-bitty consider them using a.
Directory federation services this goes hand-in-hand with other active directory
...directory...to work with the everybody's doing with api
and the fact that you can go into one access point in...of different silos all active
...directory people kind...ignore so we will review that as well.
Thank you david.
Run slower
ok so this is a travel up you might have seen it before it's a simple
...as flashy as the one that we've seen in the keynote with the three three-d
princeton but it has the same core principles and functionality that...want to show
...right now so let's go imagine the scenario you guys are
dev you need to create and app this is the apt eventually will create and
depth requirements is to be able to thank you travel order
...manage travel trouble request basically for employees within the company
...obviously you need to get the company all the customers information from
...force you need to integrate with office three sixty
five for the sharepoint because you want of documentation keep track and all of that there's always
...database on premise that you need to manage and you want to have I want to give access to
external xyz well one third-party vendors to be able to
...the site so this is what we created...super exciting
...visualization but basically covers everything...said.
...integration although
...coming from so force whose pick one.
Speaker different one good let's see...from home.
Kind of like to fly.
It style...one...but this will be good enough in
terms of accommodation and that's put some nodes so we can...
This-is bill demo we'll...because take one was earlier this morning when I was
Let's say I want to florio six-week.
Come back...week and recall so here
...saves do some bunch of work behind-the-scenes and,
...kind of done.
at the information now can see we added the sharepoint...really amazing again
just for showing that we can doesn't necessarily need to do something meaningful but curator
the word document with all the information from here can you can kick a workflow
can imagine using...logic up some doing a bunch of other stuff on top of that actually automate
...extra-extra things
...functionality you can also figure out page we expose a web
if api layer here mobile application can plug into the and everybody
...have fun...so this is the app I've been through memorably exciting I'm not going to
show the fancy logic editor workflow because they don't have one with
this application but for the purpose of what I'm going to show
is good enough so if I look at the app most of your have raise your hands I'm going
to the extremely quick this is the portal?
...what's in the of this portal what...old...classics so this one has maybe different
...but this is...application you can see
...access that little bit before them on right now monitoring nothing
you with this app this...bit different if...already
familiar or seeing some of the difference between what I'm going to show what's exist
to the cool so next thing I have an up I have a newer version of
...we of obviously we have we when we build application we do it
more than just demos and more than just keynote we actually have versions...to
...deployment reproduction so,
how do we want to help folks when they coming to deploying...production?
Basically we work with the...depose...
varvery powerful in terms of controlling giving a lot of
controlling...in the way that how you
...of the player application into production so bunch of...raise your hand that are
...using websites how many are using sloth.
Any kind of floats only...ok for let's see this...what is this thing so the
forman...basically essentially it's another sites another
...I have trouble production alternate and it will open up and you
...see here is a blade and displayed is basically trouble production
...different url you can see here
is a different sites different setting and...water stuff but when
I properly configured is what you happen to what you'll see the
...has the next version of my application and you can hook it
...ci and,...integration deployment and bunch of stuff and david I so
...you spanking radiohead were...somewhere I can
...so they will has a great session tomorrow exactly this time to
...so actually talk about all the operation how do we deploy how do we do all
this management around what I want to show it just what is...basically?
Solve the...that we have...so we have slots how does it look what are the
...have slog basically I have a site let me go here and actually go to my.
Direct url.
...a life's a little bit easier and this is the staging
ok.
instead of going to the canonical name I went to trouble ...hyphen production
...demo piazza websites always another websites so the trouble can't
also dot net and I did the same thing with the alternate...
what you can see is that there is a difference between those two sites
...the differences kind of visible one-in-two
...the new version has a big as a green as a
green background so what does staging do and just in case you guys...
to have somevisual aids staging basically allows you to take I have assigned
...production site and what staging allows me to do is to set up the staging
The green site hence the green.
...running a little bit too fast and snickering and...
service digital production and as you can see you can actually target each one of them separately so you can test the
...you can work it out you can do whatever you want with the site in
due time when you're happy we basically allow you to swap...swapping.
What happened...you'll so swapping basically take and...the...so now the green
becomes a production and what used to be staging which is
...become the book so this is swapping together at using it
your morgan...complex...because it will say once and stuff imagine you have
an issuing production discover the horrendous bug you can immediately
robotic everything works cool okay so?
So, I have my staging site or go back to...production...and I can hear the
...button toyed flipping betweenproduction
...destination and obviously if I have multiples sloppily can do that as well one of the new thing that we
...released recently as a web is the ability to see the preview of the changes so this
will let you see the difference in configuration between the two slots...you have the
...staging slot that we're going to production vice versa, for example,
if you want to have a different database...string between the two of them if you wish
or a different setting or anything similar to that will be different from staging into
production you can see all...all the differences in between the staging...see the new
...values so forth I'm not actually going to swap because what was being around for over a
year and swapping for over a year so on the show something else.
So, we're going to swap.
A different thing that we have.
To the following future so
the inherent problem with swapping is that if you have a large sites or heavy traffic
sight or whatever you want to call it which is important to you and you
swap you basically take a hundred-percent of your traffic and
put it into a new version of your...now you desolate and everybody happy and we
are cool but sometimes bad things do happen ...the happening production...
to go to ages session aging the work...a...on friday last session of
...on the last ...but we've really good session how to actually troublesome
stuff to try to avoid that what we're saying is basically instead of?
Instead of taking everything and just swapping in between the two version you have the
ability basically to...control so now...can actually go ahead and
deploy little bits into...portion of that
into your traffic so let's go how does it work.
Just showed you feature...
Routing already have the alternate
...receive zero traffic I can do anything between zero to a
...I can do fife...can do then.
I can do zero-point-one and as soon as I lose the focus you see
the production received the rest of it so,
this is very powerful feature for the purpose of this demo output fifty.
...to show that they can.
He deceive cool okay so for...actually go back to this
sites and, what we'll do is we'll go to the main?
Rural.
This is the trouble control...dot net.
And, I have landed by chance on the production
...so to see this in action actually what I want to show you a
little bit behind-the-scene it's important because...we'll explain.
So, what you see here basically is a cookie we call a techniques
...and production the...product and we have...its
...eighty-two point something so it's like eighty two percent make sense?
Let me copy this...I want to show you basically is if you coming as a separate user.
Or different session you might end up with different values.
What I'm doing right now...basically?
I'm going to
change those values so instead of eighty-two let's say we're going to one-point-two which is under
fifteen now and I'm going to refresh we're going to happen is I'm going to a
hits the alternates like the staging site nowI'm still the same url.
All right.
And, that's basically what you can do with
...slowly increase...to the point you're happy you either merger changes
you swapping whatever you want they will definitely have mortal about us okay.
So, with that in mind.
Now we have our to sites.
...running and we covered a bunch of stuff.
...bunch of stuff if something bad happen and of
course for enough so let's see let's a little a quick recap on what we've seen so
far so we have we have...apps...over here this up
...some third-party services...force the user...sixty-five and
has a database can be access from the internet I haven't showed you about the reason actually directorial
showed you right now and we also have and windows server xx
...because we do the real...because in real-life most companies have some sort
of directory which is other than other active directory you definitely want to do that
to allow this wonderful thing that you single sign on between your brought
...user and you can actually
...everything and congestion...so let's see let's see that really quick?
So, to show as...going to go to the classic portal and,
I have a directory here.
...my directory sorry.
And, if I look at the directory domains...for example,
you guys can see here's the...web call and if I look at
the director integration you'll see that I'm ...
Into actual active directory domain server all showed you a little bit in
a few and, the reason this is important is because now I can use micro
...and do as a so among
...my regular called credential to everything else so my trouble up my
...sixty-five so forth so you can imagine that you can add more and more on top of the of
...bunch of stuff in terms ofin terms of
...this is important because everything that we've seen in the demos and,
everything is in the sorry...were up services and they were talking about the ability to
expose api and get from all different sources are actually being funneled through
the identity broker that has been managed by the active directory?
Which is rotor important called so we've seen that?
We've seen an okay so what.
Actually, you know, what...
Cool so this is a traveler.
But, this is not a regular what you call standard works like this
in sort of way...has something some new or some aspect of some
...some use into it and let me covered at right now?
And, the best way to show it basically will be,
for example,...kind of hint into that...going to the upsettinggo to the
application setting and what you'll see here is this is the app
...me on...connections
...and what you see here is ten dot
zero-point-six...address directly within the...sequel connections
and which...I'm connecting through some sort...resource in a close
...this is than regular ip and sorry it's another regular internet others right server same thing
ever over here with my other...strength?
If I look at the site today with other websites you have the ability to use
a hybrid connection or virtual or vp and virtual network basically but,
there's no virtual let result hybrid collection configure...this box.
And, there's no virtual network configure news on this work cedar so,
how does this kind of work so with that in mind?
What I want to a...is basically go ahead
internal topology what we've seen we have an app we have the staging
site and somehow these things are connected to some sort of form
premise resources we got the...and we are somehow connected to
...so in order to do that I'm very happy to introduce you to
...service environments which is a brand...feature that we actually launching to
the in preview and, what is...environment you're
asking so of service environment is available under premium
...a new premium to your feature and what it gives you the
...is a dedicated computers just for you
...for everybody who runs a raises their hand and
...are already running websites today you guys are running in a skill
units or your guys are running in what we call a
...environment the...even when you go into basic or standards
and you get your on dedicated servers
you still sharing part of the system including a front-end file servers a bunch of
other management and there are some limitation that comes with that you can scale more
than ten vehemence if you guys have seen within the portal there are some network
...limitations so forth so
...up service environment what you're getting basically is your
own dedicated compute resource you can think of it is your own private
...websites warm-up story of service deployment dedicated
only for for-you and, we did we basically increase the scanning options you can go
to tent warning fifty...whatever you want and we have
our directly creating the application within a virtual network as part
as being of the virtual network which was not being which was that something you can do
up until today we should give you hint about how we actually doing stuff?
Right so if you conceptual model and then we can actually go see some of the stuff
...an example so we have we have we have...up service of...mobile a web
and api doesn't really matter and a few of them and those are what we call running within an
up service plan so you may or may not know maturity using udp service plan
...your raises their hand of service plan what used to be called web hosting
plan...if you look at dpi it's actually called...from but
...all the...okay and they define basically askew is the kind of what pricing
...you're going through standard basic premium free.
with that skew you're defining the features that you have number of...common stores
...many sites so forth ...going to choose your compute resource how many cores one core to
core how many memory...with those and an and lasting is basically you can
scale kinescope today before up services between one and
then okay without services basically...can have any number of serviceman this is nothing new
without services specifically I can go to have a premium I can go
through a pfour which gives me eight core and sixteen fourteen gigs of memory and I
can scale to eight or eighty doesn't really matter and that point.
One more nn endnote that's it for now let's.
One more note...when you run the up service
environment ski basically the skew will be always premium by the by
different...you like it or not because of services part of for premium.
So, this travel application actually runs as part
...up service environment note this up service environment doesn't seem to have a lot
remember this preview but it's really, really powerful and we'll see
significant it has a few apps right now it has a small demo up and has
a trouble troll production up...has a few service plan and actually see the
service when associate with this...environment?
It has few of them and only two of them actually running the sites that we have.
One of the thing you'll notice is that in terms of sub domain we have created
adifferent sub domain fob service environment so this is buy-up service environment...and it I
choose ...is for placeholder and we have other website
...which is usual you'll notice that it is already have a virtual network and we audience subset
...be created a submits into which you can also in which we actually
deploy the observers environment which is essentially.
Essentially cloud service.
Okay, so,
how you want to create a new...service environment very simple go to the plus?
The mobile...you go up service environment you the name.
We are trying to find the of virtual network that works for-you if not will create one for
you...we also create a submit into which we can deploy
...service environment...cover that one we're actually going to see the virtual
...data scale is one of the interesting...that...to talk about
so here in terms of scale you get to choose the.
Size of the vm and the amount of the vm that-you want-to basically for all if you're
...to run so it's not just a single up when you go ahead and change-up service plan
...that magic basically
you can control a bunch of worker pools we can see here on top of that you have the
...when you run today without service...without
up service environments you're running...again says a multi-band environment you're showing the
...with everybody else and therefore you don't really see them we on them we minutes
...was still manager everything here for-you however,
because this is a cluster you get to manage and choose your front so basically
you can go ahead and figure out what kind of front and you want to run to...we are blocking the
sm ...for performance so, forth so...propose.
The three worker pools and basically the can see we have a variety
of scale option here so we have
four nudges three so you can scale up as well as...so,
can go ahead and you can choose like hey,
you know, what this will be my the first so more workable one is good our
...to will be my staging environment...or...three will be
...production...go with the...they can...
so rather said the worker pools I can go ahead and actually said the scale itself so by default...have
...vans were deployed for you to front-end and to workable and
...unworkable one you can do whatever you want with that and notice that I can run and eigen
...is a...so this could before but this could be ...twenty-three?
And, the seventeen...sixteen good.
And, you get the idea right so you can define a worker pool also
...can have up to fifty free from a can staking the three is kind of weird but
put aside for a second can epub to fifty-three of
...and it's a policies...obviously will be able to...in the future this
is being deployed into west us which will then go ahead and creates
...environment deploying this takes a little bit of time as you can imagine what I'm going
...production?
But, once I have we can already have...have one
...demo I can just go ahead and ed website just like a
web app for mobile or whatever you guys...just as easy.
I need to...the name.
...and then I go into a service plan majority existwhich defines
...everything else basically if I want to change the service...for a second this will give me some
opportune to talk about location so what you see here basically is that
up service environment in was to us and...other one is to in the
...your which...see in the...or later than them the thing is that?
The thing is that.
You can think of this is like a new virtual location this environment
existing list us and you can deploy your sites into the and.
So, reflector
...one the...good...ok.
And, creates...so...creates.
And, we'll talk about the worker...so.
We have the...so service plan is to be attached to a worker...and,
basically this is the difference between the existence stuff and what we have so within
of service environment you have work...workable can be a small medium larger extra-large
...scene and you can have almost as many as...you have plenty of them and
...few of those there are three worker pools to which you can
...your application so if I go to?
...the...is being...good timing so here's a site.
Click...a...
...deploying...whatever you want nothing changes from the perspective
anything that does changes when I want to go now and talk about the service plan.
And, I talk about the worker pool now I can actually choose which worker pool
...notice that within that you
can't really change the scaling is you would expect because of
your running within...a predefine workable,
workable sorry so you get all of them basically what you want to choose you can
carvel if you want differently but you guys get the idea so...service...
industrial worker pool and you can define the side-of-the-road...the sort of the europe service...
All right cool so this was the observers environment in knoxville at
least from the worker perspective if we're going back to the app and we'll see how the app is mapping to the
...environment so we have a or application we have the staging environment we
have this row but now we understand this whole thing is kind of deployed within
subnet so I have the application service environment subnet.
Subnet number-one for the vm and
for my database they're all running within the same context of the virtual
network no more the need to disclose at the new deploy the vp
and gateway on a dedicated server that will go ahead actually and
...will go ahead and talk to a gateway on the virtual network to talk of any assets you can directly
...them within the virtual network
...one so now it's time to actually go and talk about called the complexity of the virtual
networks virtual networks by the way are available new portal.
Somewhere around here.
However, person preferences and...of functionality
they have more to...more to...in the classic portals...just use that.
So, these are these are virtual network that we use.
If you look at the configuration what you'll see.
In a psych.
So, this just show you guys how a messy we are and we
learn with time and we created this virtual...year-ago and this is the previous
other space or the exerted is the first...and...we
...zero to one is basically the...in which we deployedthe sequel and the v and,
...sorry the vm the to isdn one of them is
...one is the domain controller on...that for users and,
this is a new one way and this is a new address space of
...dot one basically for the application service environment toward the subnet and there's another
wofford will actually going to
...a second now to show you then the bluffing you anything like that.
Here the actual.
Vehemence thanks for sodium over here.
Virtual machines here is like the sequel,
for example, server user dashboard.
Sequel server you can see the...zero-point-six.
That's the one actually can go into.
Already...dp into the...a...you guys can see
...fig use the ip and if...refers this query can
productions at another item which was showed show number ten which is the.
The think number two...new travel that we've just created so
Sequel.
Database runs on a as vm that runs within
...within the virtual network and application server now...the
...up service environment with the website
can directly connect because of the network breath or just therewhich makes of work?
Called the same way I have access to the domain controller work you guys get the
What next...
Why not?
If you look at dashboard of the network of the virtual network what you'll see is.
What you'll see here basically is the is that this network this virtual network
...connected to another one in north europe and we'll see that are in the second this
...traffic mandarin...other stuff but you can see the sql
in different subnet and all the other submitting here okay so?
We've been hearing a lot from customers other than they want more machines and more powerful and which
...environment gives them is
...one better control over the network and most likely all the most common as
...we're hearing is that they want to be able to hides
their sites meaning they don't want to allow access from the internet to those
...those...your product...your production or
...those...it doesn't really matter and there's a lot of stuff and you can do you can put any kind amin
we are specific about wife which is where application firewall but you can imagine
you can place any kind of network...the
...manager into the virtual network in front of your sites
...basically protector application from bunch of stuff, you know,
those scanning?
And, you any formal for you know,
kind of attacks ...provider far will as well but, you can imagine
...puts any other elements over but the idea is that with
whether we thought the often can actually hides those
sites from the public internet and you can either go from corporate...can actually
a allow only traffic that will flow throughexternal will go into
...go through often go through europe to your site.
So, to see that.
...all that which is good.
The network team has created.
The...other the sorry...network immigrated
network security groups which are extremely powerful not...not available through the
...through any of the portal you can do them through only through only through partial.
So, what I want to show you basically is this I go to?
...service and cloud service has on what often
...looming if I go to the dashboard for a second.
And, this is a cloud service...is being deployed into the same virtual network
and we'll use that this...have to windows server.
Two thousand twelve and basically all they do is just reversed proxy
...emulating a wife because when we came up to deploy a real one it costs about four
thousand dollars so we said no.
Ok, so, if I go here I go to my...
Real quick...show you is the
...of domains that we...registered.
...it a few of...web there...
In case there is travel...vtwo for the traffic manager and
there's trouble production which is the one...we have of seen.
All right so we're going to do next is basically go to partial.
And,...this...basically.
I've already set up and network security group
...yes so what I want to do is basically apply it.
Which will be?
The applying so I'm getting my
...security groups name restricts west us up spay app access basically
...a certain networks security group to my virtual, virtual nets
virtual network which is down demo and I'm going to specifically restricted to
one submit which is the...that we're having.
So, this takes...
While this happens.
I'll use the time basically to go ahead and talk about.
Traffic manager and how do we integrate everything and bring multiple regions together?
So, if we look at the end points and will look at them again shortly?
You see there are three endpoints there is one problem production eu which is the one in
north europe there is droll production...which we've been using those
...and there is the...those the wife which is the
...which is basically what makes the
...the cloud services we've talked about okay.
So, if I look, for example, in the app here.
...production in eu a is basically website
...and this one again is
...of it's basically part of?
Another
up service environment but being deployed in dublin basically.
And, to show you that.
I can do this can go and into.
...login successfully because we'll be able to login because we have
this thing cooking goes into a different site.
That may not go through a little bit of standard...when do.
Do...look up just to go from here?
...teaching.
Well-conceived and basically this will give you actually good thing what we're deploying is was crowed
the bthree and if you're familiar with our deployment if you look at the publishing profile you'll figure out that you should
...you should recognize this prefix as well...the bthree because usually you see a number
...number like zero one eleven seventeen whateverover
here's a little bit of a good in the cloud that this is basically the deployment in which we manage
for-you of the observers environments and here's the address if I try to if I
try to let's see?
We can go to my other window.
I can go ahead and try to find the...control
sony what you'll see you'll see comes with difference depends on the time of day and how
traffic manager figured out what you can see...variants
...information here like one ip address which is...for which to the cloud
...which is always the observers environment and different one which is the
...is the...
So, what we do is basically if we go here this is...our app?
...this is the app itself just another work-site if I look at the
...in what will be interesting if this another best practice worded works and
just to show is that this is use the same connection thing remember this
...runs right now in europe...connect over the vp
...network the site to site as...as kind of supposed to happen with the...
network manager to west us to the database and to the
database to the vm actually running and...
And, if you look at the virtual networks.
Either one of them.
...able to see that ...connectivity points to
...from one-point-one virtual network this is the one
...us points to the one in europe and voice-overs
...so now I believe that the partial script is run what I want to show you is?
Is the details so we're going to see here basically is the details of the security
group which is request us and you can see that on thing allowing to
use overlying only...from...https two-one thirty-seven which is the ip
address of the wife basically there's completes
...virtual...to virtual network this is how the worse than the...or
communicating and everything else is pretty much blocked so that in mind?
If enough time has pass.
Let's see.
All right good so if you remember earlier this was not the
aggregated okay so what happen is this is the is
this is the north europe still working I had traffic manager pointing
to roles one will directly on the
observers environment's site which is this one and the other one was the wife
now since I apply my security group now you can no longer access the
sites directly you have to go through the wife to be able to
...the site?
And, how does it look?
Basically using over here.
So, this is the production of refresh this and this
will now be spinning for a while until times out.
And, if I go to a difference tab and I...directly.
The composer web domain this will actually work.
And, which look actually lenin omni?
On the...the alternate site works together earlier.
And, this one runs in west us on the other one runs in order to groups.
All right.
So,...that in mind.
I think we've come to a full-circle.
And, what we've seen is basically we have of service
environment's which is deployed into a virtual network and then it gets all the
benefits of virtual network across everything that other has to offer?
we have to sites also have one...deployed into physical location and due to different
up service environment one in...to...northrop...traffic manager on top of
that and that's...achieved high availability there is
...are kind of option if one node goes down hopefully not the worst one because that's where
the databases...you guys get the idea the best practices just show off how
we can do and how we can do withwe have other session covering some more of the topics of...one of the
hire availability all right so to summarize observers environment's of
...premium theorem...offer its dedicated compute resource...they could compute
...net they can network resources directly for you
you're completely isolated from anybody else...global schedulers lot-of scale scale-up
...across the and the nice thing about it is all the great
web features and capabilities...you already are using are just
going to work just as so this is good news is support web mobile api
...we plus?
And, it's available to the...a probably preview all right.
So, that in mind under resources that are available
...track and please provide your feedback for
the session and if you guys have any questions.
Thank you very much.